A Guide to the Papers of the Low Moor Iron Company
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Records
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B, C", incl. D. S. Cook, David Baker, Earle C. Bacon - Engineer, H. H. Babcock Co., Cumberland Lumber Co., W. A. Cummings, 1893 -1906 (Box Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", incl. D. S. Cook, Thomas P. Conard, Cochrane Roller Mills Co., Copeland & Bacon, Craing City Improvement Co., Clinton Firebrick Works, 1891 -1895 (Box Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. Mountain State Scale & Specialty Co., J. M. Mossman Co., Mount Savase Firebrick, Morris Wheeler & Co., Morrison Machinery & Supply Co., Walter D. Moses & Co., Moore Lime Co., J. C. Moorehead Lumber Co., 1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B, M", incl. C. G. Blake & Co., George Blackwell & Sons, Miller Supply Co., David Blustein, Moore Lime Co., 1901 -1906 (Box Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", incl. Best Manufacturing Co., Bird Iron Co., Big Bend Coal Co., Best Light Co., Berger Manufacturing Co., Bessemer Coke Co., Beaver Valley Metal Co., JHC Barr, A. J. Beckley Co., Baldwin Locomotive Works, David Baker Metal Engineer, Barnett Co., Banks Supply Co., 1903 -1906; (3 folders) (Box Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F", incl. Fayetteville Coal & Coke, Firecreek Coal & Coke, Fort Pitt Forge Co., The Fox Pater Co., France Packing Co., Fairbanks Co., H. L. Frost, Allegheny County Treasurers Office, 1902 -1904; (2 folders) (Box Box 74)
  - Hunter B. Frischkorn, 1902 -1904; (3 folders) (Box Box 74)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Coal Co., 1899 -1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 74)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, 1906 (Box Box 74)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. and Chesapeake & Ohio Coal & Coke Co., 1904 -1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. Morris-Wheeler & Co., E. K. Morris & Co., Morris-Woodhull & Co., Mountain State Business College, J. S. Mundy Co., A. E. Myers, Mutual Life Insurance, Murray Iron Works, J. C. Moorhead Lumber Co., M. M. Morrison; Low Moor - Bills of Lading from C. & O. Railroad, Moore Lime Co., William S. Moore & Sons, Monarch Iron & Steel Co., Missouri Belting Co., Miller Supply Co., Miller School of Albemarle, Erskine Miller, Midland Steel Co., Miller Lead Co., Albert Miller Groceries, 1902 -1906; (7 folders) (Box Box 75)
  - Dalton Nash & Co. to President Cargill and Hibbert, 1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 76)
  - Dalton Nash & Co. to E. C. Means, 1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 76)
  - Cyclone Drill Co. to George T. Wicks - manager of the mines, 1907 (Box Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", incl. Justice Cox Jr., D. S. Cook Princess Pig Iron, Coburn Trolly Track Manufacturing Co., Collins Manufacturing Co., Consolidated Timelock Co., C. G. Cooper & Co., Cooke & Co., Justice Cox Iron & Steel, Covington National Bank, Covington Light & Fuel Co., Covington Machine Co., 1895 -1899; (2 folders) (Box Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "W", incl. D. J. Williams & Co., Willard & Ford, R. D. Wood & Co., Winifred Coal Co., S. R. White & Bro., W. W. Winchester, A. F. Withrow Co., 1896 -1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 77)
  - Covington Machine Co. and Covington National Bank, 1897 -1899 (Box Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C, Z", incl. Crescent Supply Co., Covington Ice Co., Crescent Steel Co., G. A. Zirckel, Crane Elevator Co., 1898 -1906 (Box Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "W, Y, Z" incl. Zainas Paint Co., C. H. Zehender - President, Yellow Pine Lumber Co., M. L. B. Young, Woodward & Sons, 1904 -1906 (Box Box 77)
  - Covington National Bank - bills and receipts, 1895 -1898; (2 folders) (Box Box 77)
  - Covington Machine Co., 1895 -1896 (Box Box 77)
  - Low Moor Iron Co. wage scales from the General Managers file, 1914 -1919 (Box Box 78)
  - U.S. Shipping Board Emergency Fleet concerning Low Moor shipping, 1918 (Box Box 78)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture from Low Moor General Managers file, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 78)
  - Traffic Dept. of Low Moor from the General Managers file, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 78)
  - Telephones concerning Low Moor, 1917 March -Aug. (Box Box 78)
  - Taxes concerning Low Moor from the General Managers file, 1919 April (Box Box 78)
  - Shawinigan Electric Products Co., 1916 Nov. -Dec. (Box Box 78)
  - State Board of Health to Low Moor, 1918 Sept. (Box Box 78)
  - Smokeless Fuel Co. from General Managers file, 1916 -1919 (Box Box 78)
  - Scrap for Low Moor, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 78)
  - Rogers-Brown Co. from the General Managers file, 1916 -1919 (Box Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", incl. Bell & Catlit, C. Bargamin, 1887 (Box Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B-D, G", incl. Driscoll & Dixon, Crane Elevator Co., D. S. Cook - supplies, Gordon & Son, 1887 -1904 (Box Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H, J, K", incl. Jockham - Supt - Dolly Ann Mines, D. L. Huddlestun, Michael Kiulighan, Havemeyer Sugar Co., James River Cement Works, 1887 (Box Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M-N, R-S", incl. E. M. Nettleton, J. J. Montague George A. Smith, Newport News & Mississippi Valley Co., Southern Railway Supply Co., Thomas W. Stils, 1887 (Box Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "T, V, W", incl. Low Moor Iron Co. to Dixon Supt from E. C. Means, 1887 -1908 (Box Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N-R", incl. Olive Hill Firebrick Co., Osborne Burke, Ricketts & Banks, 1896 -1901 (Box Box 79)
  - Low Moor letters from G. T. Wickes, manager of the mines, to Shirkley, 1906 (Box Box 79)
  - Low Moor Employment correspondence, incl. importation of immigrant labor and black business history, 1906 -1907 (Box Box 79)
  - Low Moor Elevator Co., 1907 (Box Box 79)
  - Employees concerning Low Moor, 1906 (Box Box 79)
  - Electrical Plant of Low Moor, 1906 (Box Box 79)
  - Express receipts from Wickes, 1906 -1907 (Box Box 79)
  - Expense account of George T. Wickes, manager of the mines, 1905 -1907 (Box Box 79)
  - Employment agencies for inquiring into Low Moor employment, 1907 (Box Box 79)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, western office - orders and correspondence, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad - orders and correspondence, 1905 -1906; (3 folders) (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, eastern office - orders and correspondence, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, from J. W. Averill (agent) - correspondence, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, from E. D. Hotchkiss, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad to C. W. Johns - Assistant Engineer for C. & O about engineering problems, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad from C. W. Walker - Supt. - orders and correspondence, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad from J. H. Carlisle - superintendent - orders and correspondence, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad - orders for cars, coke, etc., 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad correspondence - shipping and returning orders, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Paint for Low Moor (sample colors), 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Low Moor - Post Offices, 1907 (Box Box 80)
  - Low Moor personal injuries, 1906 -1907 (Box Box 80)
  - Low Moor Quarry Houses, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Low Moor Iron Co. prop timber, 1906 (Box Box 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, incl. correspondence from J. H. Carlisle Supt., J. R. Cary - Supt., E. W. Grice - Supt., C. C. Walker - Supt., E. D. Hotchkiss, Averill - Supt., 1905 -1906; (13 folders) (Box Box 80A)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Coal & Coke Co. from M. O. Brooks, general manager, 1906 (Box Box 80A)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad weights, 1906 -1907 (Box Box 80A)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Coal Agency, incl. correspondence from Hopkins, 1901 -1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 80A)
  - C. & O. Coal & Coke Co., western office, 1906 (Box Box 80A)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad - orders and correspondence, 1905; (3 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - C. & O. Coal & Coke Co. and C. & O. Coal Agency Co., 1905 (Box Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", incl. Carnegie Steel Works, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, Calahan Supply Co., Philip Carey Manufacturing Co., Cleveland Cliffs Iron Co., 1895 -1905; (2 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. Erskine Miller - President of Thurmond Coal Co., 1887 (Box Box 81)
  - C. & O. Railroad and Taylor Iron & Steel Co., 1903 -1904 (Box Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "T", incl. Thompson & Son, Town of Covington, Tredegar Iron Works, Thomsen Chemical Co., Taylor Wagon Works, Taylor Iron & Steel Co., Tugarat Firebrick Co., Trenton Iron Co., Tweeddale Water Softening Co., 1903 -1904; (2 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - Baldwin-Baughman, 1897 -1898 (Box Box 82)
  - Baldwin Locomotive Works, 1893 -1899 (Box Box 82)
  - Bobson & Boyulon, 1893 -1899 (Box Box 82)
  - Bradford to C. N. Brown, 1890 -1899 (Box Box 82)
  - Edward Brown - gauges, 1891 -1899 (Box Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", incl. E. V. Brown, Bryan Mfg. Co., Bucyrus Co., Buena Vista Fireclay Co., Buena Vista Mining Co., Buffalo Forge Co., Henry Bulkley - engineer, Bullard & Co., Bullock & Crenshaw, Bundy Mfg. Co., Burckhardt Co., W. J. Burton Co. Burt Mfg. Co., Burpee Co., Butler & Bosher, D. N. Byers Machine Co., Byrnes & Co., 1891 -1899; (6 folders) (Box Box 82)
  - Appraisal of assets of various small iron companies, 1901 (Box Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S", incl. Southwark Foundry & Machine Co., Southern Railway Supply Co., Southern Clay Product Co., Southern Iron & Equipment Co., M. L. Snyder, Spinney-Virtve & Co., T. R. N. Speck, Standard Oil Co., Standard Thermometer & Electric Co., Stern & Co., Steel Rail Supply Co., Starkeu & Sexton - coal, wood & feed, Starkeis Dixie Plow Word, Stanley & Patterson, B. F. Stockdon & Bros. - machinists & founders, Stow Mfg. Co., Strecker Bros. - harnesses, J. D. Strett & Co.- oils and greases, E. S. and F. L. Sublett, Sullivan Oil Co., Stromberg Carlson Telephone Mfg. Co., Struthers Wells & Co., James Swank - American Iron & Steel Assoc., Swift & Co., 1895 -1907; (6 folders) (Box Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Standard", incl. Standard Oil Co., Standard Typewriter Co., Standard Pneumatic Tool Co., Standard Carbon Co., Standard Plaster Co., Standard Scales, 1896 -1899 (Box Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H, J, M", incl. L. M. Miller - well driller, Erskine Miller, Natural Bridge Co., National Geographic Society, T. G. Harrington - well driller, 1906 -1913 (Box Box 83)
  - Dalton - Nash & Co., 1906 May (Box Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", incl. E. I. Dupont & Co., E. Dillion & Sons, Detroit, Toledo & Ironton Railway Co., Dickinson Firebrick, Dodge Coal Co., Detroit Supply & Foundry Co., 1906 May -Sept. (Box Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "T-V", incl. Union Mining Co., Vehlings method of conveying metal, H. B. Underwood machinist, Vulcan Iron Works, Virginia Iron Co., Virginia Carolina Chemical Co., Tredegar Iron Works, Turner Co., 1899 (Box Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", incl. McAllister & Bell - dealers in grain and fertilizer, J. T. McCabe, Alexander McIntock & Irvine, McClure Co., McLanghan & Stone, Peter McLaren McDowell & Co., Longdale Iron Co. from McGuffen - agent, Ashland Coal & Iron Railway Co., McNab & Harbin, Thomas Mechan & Son, Meehan Boiler & Construction Co., Metallic Cap Mfg. Co., 1891 -1900; (5 folders) (Box Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", incl. Baldwin Locomotive Works, Basic City Iron Works, C. R. Baird & Co., Baughman & Co., Baker Bros. & Co., Baltimore United Oil Co., Ball & Co., Barton Wireworks, Barlows Patent Shipping Blanks, Baughman Stationery Co., Bell & Catlett, Bertha Mineral Co., Best-Fox & Co. - Bronze, Berlin Iron Works, Bethlehem Iron Co., Bickerton & Co., Bignall & Reeler, 1891 -1896; (4 folders) (Box Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "American", incl. American Iron & Steel Co., American Hay & Grain Co., American Locomotive Co., American Tobacco Co., American Cotton Oil Works, American Spiral Pipe Co., American Pig Iron Storage Warrent Co., American Cart & Foundry Co., 1904 -1906; (2 folders) (Box Box 86)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A", incl. Allegheny Ore & Iron Co., American Car & Foundry Co., American Cotton Oil Co., American Cement Tile Mfg. Co., Allegheny Brick Co., Adams Bros.-Payne Co., Allis Chalmers Co., Austin Powder Co., Austin Western Co., Ashland Firebrick Co., Atlas Engine Works, Anchor Buggy Co., Ashland Steel Co., 1905 -1906; (3 folders) (Box Box 86)
  - Low Moor Iron Co. from George T. Wickes manager of the mines, to E. C. Means and S. G. Cargill, incl. information on importation of foreign labor and labor unrest in Kay Moor Mines, 1905 -1906; (3 folders) (Box Box 87)
  - Nash Isham & Co. - shipping orders, correspondence, receipts, 1911 -1912; (2 folders) (Box Box 87)
  - Provident Life & Accident Insurance to Cargill, 1902 March -1906 May; (2 folders) (Box Box 88)
  - Correspondence from Robert Parrish & Son to E. C. Means and S. G. Cargill, 1901 April -1906 May; (5 folders) (Box Box 88)
  - Correspondence from Princess Iron Co. to Means, 1902 June -May (Box Box 88)
  - Correspondence from Pickards, Mather & Co. to Means, 1902 July -1906 May (Box Box 88)
  - Pierce & Akers Co., 1903-1905 (Box Box 88)
  - Post-Glover Electric Co. and Portsmouth Foundry & Machine Works, 1887 Jan. -1906 Feb. (Box Box 88)
  - Portsmouth Harbison-Walker to E. C. Means, 1903 Feb. -1906 April (Box Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Q-S", 1887 Jan. -Aug. (Box Box 88)
  - Pitt Mfg. Co.; Pitt & Scott Ltd.; Pittsburgh Boiler Scale Resolvent Co.; Pittsburgh Gate & Supply Co.; Pittsburgh Rail Supply Co.; Pittsburgh Spring & Steel Co.; Pittsburgh Supply Co., 1901 March -1906 March (Box Box 88A)
  - Robert Poole & Son; William Pollock Co.; Pontiac Spring & Wagon Works, 1902 Aug. -1905 Aug. (Box Box 88A)
  - Pennsylvania Steel; J. Wesley Pullman, 1902 May -1906 March (Box Box 88A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Pe-Pi", 1902 March -1906 March (Box Box 88A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Pa", 1902 April -1906 June (Box Box 88A)
  - George Pyles; Pyles & Smith, 1905 May -1906 May (Box Box 88A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Po-Pr", 1902 Sept. -1906 April (Box Box 88A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-W" to Means and Cargill, 1901-1906 (Box Box 88A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "E", 1897 March -1906 Dec.; (5 folders) (Box Box 89)
  - Edgar Zinc Co., 1899 Dec. -1906 Nov.; (2 folders) (Box Box 89)
  - Eimer & Amend, 1899 Nov. -1906 Oct. (Box Box 89)
  - J. W. Ellison, 1900 March -1906 Dec. (Box Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ea-S" to Cargill, 1900 Nov. -1906 Jan. (Box Box 89A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B-U", 1901 March -1906 Jan. (Box Box 89A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ja-Je", 1901 June -1904 Oct. (Box Box 89A)
  - Jeffrey Mfg. Co., 1901 Feb. -1904 Aug.; (2 folders) (Box Box 89A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Jo-Ju", 1901 July -1904 July (Box Box 89A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Johns-Johnson", 1901 March -1904 Sept. (Box Box 89A)
  - Jones & Laughlin Steel, 1901 April -1904 March (Box Box 89A)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box Box 89A)
  - Correspondence "A-R" to Low Moor and Cargill, 1900 Jan. -1906 May (Box Box 90)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", 1899 Nov. -1901 April; (3 folders) (Box Box 90)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S-W", 1902 June -1907 April (Box Box 90)
  - Polly Ann Contracts, 1899 Nov. -1901 March (Box Box 90)
  - Dalton Nash & Co., 1901 Feb. -April (Box Box 90)
  - Semet-Sulvay, Senior Powder Co., 1904 Aug. -1906 Dec. (Box Box 90)
  - Seaboard Steel Casting Co., Simmons Hardware Co., Sinnamahoning Powder Manufacturing Co., 1905 Sept. -1906 Oct. (Box Box 90)
  - O. W. Shipman, 1905 Jan. -March (Box Box 90)
  - Smith-Courtney Co., 1905 Jan. -1906 Dec. (Box Box 90)
  - Smith Fuel Co., 1905 Sept. -1906 Nov. (Box Box 90)
  - Smokeless Fuel Co., 1905 Feb. -1906 Nov. (Box Box 90)
  - Earle C. Bacon to George T. Wickes, 1906 April -1907 Nov.; (4 folders) (Box Box 91)
  - Thomas A. Mack & Co. contracts to E. C. Means, 1901 Dec. -1903 Nov.; (3 folders) (Box Box 91)
  - H. R. Durkee & Co. to E. C. Means, 1903 Feb. -Nov. (Box Box 91)
  - Contracts - carbons, 1906 Feb. -1908 April; (5 folders) (Box Box 91A)
  - Thurmond Coal Co. to H. G. Merry, 1896 Nov. -1899 Nov. (Box Box 92)
  - Tredegar Iron Works to H. G. Merry, 1898 July -1899 Nov. (Box Box 92)
  - Correspondence "Ta-Tr" to H. G. Merry, 1896 Nov. -1899 Sept. (Box Box 92)
  - J. Letch Ham to Wickes, 1905 Dec. -1907 Sept.; (2 folders) (Box Box 92)
  - Porter Clark to Wickes, 1907 Jan. -Nov. (Box Box 92)
  - Hunter B. Frischkorn to Wickes, 1907 Feb. -Nov. (Box Box 92)
  - C. P. Barnett - C. & O. Railroad to Wickes, 1905 Nov. -1907 July (Box Box 92)
  - Correspondence "B-M" to Wickes, 1903 Feb. -1907 Oct. (Box Box 92)
  - Ino Hogan & Co. to H. G. Merry, 1894 May -1895 Dec.; (3 folders) (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-W" to Merry, 1891 Nov. -1901 Aug. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hi" to Merry, 1891 July -1895 March (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hob-How" to Merry, 1891 March -1895 Dec. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hu" to Merry, 1891 Aug. -1895 Aug. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Me-My" to Merry, 1891 May -Sept. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mc" to Merry, 1901 July -Aug. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Na-O" to Merry, 1901 July -Sept. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Pa-Pu" to Merry, 1901 July -Oct. (Box Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-Boy", 1890 -1906 (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Bra-E", 1890 Feb. (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F-K", 1890 (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "L-R'', 1890 (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S ", 1890 (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "T", 1890 (Box Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "U-W", 1890 (Box Box 94)
  - McAllister & Bell, 1904 Dec. -1906 Dec.; (2 folders) (Box Box 94)
  - Merritt & Co. - bills of lading, 1906 June -Dec. (Box Box 94)
  - St. Louis Boom & Mfg. Co., 1891 Feb. -1901 June (Box Box 94)
  - George Wickes to application for draftsman - Hapgood's, 1906 March -Nov. (Box Box 94)
  - Church & Church Woodward Lawsuit, Infringement Patent to/from E. Means, 1903 Aug. -1905 March (Box Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mc", 1896 Dec. -1906 Dec. (Box Box 95)
  - C. & O. Railroad correspondence, incl. bills of lading, 1894 Nov. -1906 June; (12 folders) (Box Box 96)
  - Phillips, Isham correspondence, 1920 April -1921 Feb.; (7 folders) (Box Box 97)
  - Phillips, Isham correspondence to F. U. Humbert, 1921 March -Aug.; (4 folders) (Box Box 97A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence to Wickes, 1921 March -July (Box Box 97A)
  - List - pipe fittings for Low Moor furnace, 1911 April (Box Box 98)
  - C. & O. freight, bill of lading, 1912 Nov. (Box Box 98)
  - Miscellaneous company ads and correspondence "A-Z", 1915 Dec. -1926 March (Box Box 98)
  - U. S. Government, FTC and U. S. Public Health Service, 1919, 1930 (Box Box 98)
  - M. Weld to F. U. Humbert, Supt. of Jordan Mines, 1911 Sept -Dec. (Box Box 98)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Na", 1905 March -1906 July (Box Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ne-Nu", 1905 Jan. -1906 Aug. (Box Box 99)
  - New River Coal & Coke Co., New River Smokeless Coal, 1905 Nov. -1906 Sept. (Box Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "O", 1904 June -1906 Sept. (Box Box 99)
  - Means, Cargill to Old Dominion Iron & Nail Works Co., 1905 Jan. -1906 Oct. (Box Box 99)
  - Oglebay, Norton & Co., 1902 July -1906 Nov. (Box Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1899 May -1905 Aug. (Box Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-S", 1924 -1925 (Box Box 100)
  - Grasselli Chemical Co., 1925 April -Dec. (Box Box 100)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D-F", 1924 Nov. -1925 Dec. (Box Box 100)
  - H. A. Dalton, 1925 Jan. -Dec.; (3 folders) (Box Box 100)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G", 1925 Jan. -Dec (Box Box 100A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H", 1925 Jan. -Dec (Box Box 100A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "I-N", 1925 Jan. -Dec (Box Box 100A)
  - New River District Coal shipments, 1904 -1905 (Box Box 100A)
  - Correspondence about Low Moor, 1890 -1899 (Box Box 100A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ch-Ce", 1907 June -1914 Jan. (Box Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cro-Cru", 1908 March -1914 Jan. (Box Box 101)
  - Henry Hintner & Co., Ladd & Baker, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 101)
  - Crescent Supply Co., 1910 Feb. -1914 July (Box Box 101)
  - Crump & West Coal Co., 1911 June -1914 July (Box Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Coe-Coy", 1908 June -1914 April (Box Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Crad-Craw", 1907 Nov. -1914 April (Box Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cre-Cri", 1912 Jan. -1914 July (Box Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cu-Cy", 1907 April -1914 Feb. (Box Box 101A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", 1909 Jan. -1914 Jan. (Box Box 101A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "He-Hick", 1910 Feb. -1914 March (Box Box 101A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "High-Hir", 1909 Dec. -1914 June (Box Box 101A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hoe-How", 1907 Jan. -1914 May (Box Box 101A)
  - Correspondence about Low Moor, 1900 -1906 (Box Box 101A)
  - Correspondence about Low Moor, 1907 -1914 (Box Box 101A)
  - Correspondence about Low Moor, 1918 -1926 (Box Box 101A)
  - F. U. Humbert - contracts and amount shipped, 1919 Dec. -1921 March (Box Box 102)
  - Monthly blast records 13-C, 14-A, 15-A, 1920 Jan. -1921 March (Box Box 102)
  - G. W. Lipscomb to H. A. Dalton, 1920 Jan. -1925 Nov.; (4 folders) (Box Box 102)
  - Low Moor coke oven daily reports, 1919 Feb., April (Box Box 102)
  - Phillips, Isham, 1921 Jan. (Box Box 102)
  - Provident Life Insurance Co., 1925 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 103)
  - H. A. Dalton, Treasurer, 1925 Dec. (Box Box 103)
  - Presto Lite Co., 1925 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N-O", 1924 Nov. -1925 Aug. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "P", 1924 Aug. -1925 Dec. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Q-Son", 1925 Jan. -Dec. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Sov-Sz", 1924 June -1925 Nov. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "T", 1925 Jan. -Nov. (Box Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-B", 1917 April -1923 Aug. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", 1916 Oct. -1923 Sept. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D-F", 1917 May -1923 Oct. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G-H", 1910 Dec. -1918 July (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "I-M", 1916 Feb. -1923 Oct. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N-R", 1917 March -1923 Oct. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S-T", 1916 -1923 (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "U-W", 1916 Feb. -1923 Sept. (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous intra-company correspondence, 1917 June -1923 Sept. (Box Box 104)
  - Glen Jean Insurance Agency, 1909 June -1914 June (Box Box 104)
  - Hunter B. Frischkorn, 1917 Sept. -1918 May (Box Box 104)
  - Glamorgan Pipe & Foundry, 1912 March -1914 July; (2 folders) (Box Box 104)
  - Nash, Isham; Phillips, Isham, 1908 May -1912 March (Box Box 104)
  - Walter Wallingford, 1908 March -May (Box Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-V" from Hibbart, traffic manager; shipment made and ordered, 1918 July -1923 Dec. (Box Box 105)
  - J. R. and W. S. Johnson - orders, quoted prices, 1910 Dec. -1914 July (Box Box 105)
  - Johns-Manville - orders, technical advice on uses of asbestos at Low Moor, 1910 Jan. -1914 July (Box Box 105)
  - Jeffrey Mfg. Co. - orders, sales, advice on loaders, conveyors, etc., 1909 Nov. -1913 Sept. (Box Box 105)